And I want to take this moment to also point out, y'all, for those of you all who are creating
content, everything is not content.
Everything is not content.
And it says a lot about you on what you determine is content.
Are you a scavenger?
Are you somebody who is picking up any pieces off the ground to try to turn it into something?
That's not a look.
Or are you an actual creator?
Are you an alchemist?
Are you somebody who can actually take something that may have even been created by someone else
and expound upon it?
That can expand it into interests for other audiences?
Because this word content creator is real loose out here.
Some of y'all are content creators, but you're not a content creative.
And I want to make that distinction very clear.
A content creator is someone who is just making stuff to make the algorithm algo.
That's what you're doing.
You're just throwing anything out there.
You're grabbing it from anywhere.
And you're trying to put it out there, encase it in some sausage wrapping.
You're making hot dog level work.
It's the scraps mushed together in an attempt to make it palatable.
No, a content creative?
Ah, that's different.
A content creative is someone who is thinking not just with their pockets,
not just with their ego,
but they're thinking with their heart and mind combined
because they're making art or they're educating.